[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Italian bread called Focaccia resembles this other traditional Italian dish.", "correct_answer": "Pizza", "incorrect_answers": ["Ravioli", "Lasagna", "Biscotti"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who did Lilly want to marry back when she was a little girl in the 2003 movie The Fighting Temptations?", "correct_answer": "Michael Jackson", "incorrect_answers": ["Darrin", "Michael Jordan", "Stevie Wonder"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What Biblical prophet inspired the popular gospel song Swing Low, Sweet Chariot, composed by Wallace Willis?", "correct_answer": "Elijah", "incorrect_answers": ["Ezekiel", "Jonah", "Isaiah"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the name of the first monkey to go in outer space?", "correct_answer": "Albert I", "incorrect_answers": ["Gordo", "Sam", "Bonny"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "At birth, pandas weigh about 4 ounces and are the size of a stick of butter. Which of these is NOT true about a newborn panda?", "correct_answer": "They are grey in color.", "incorrect_answers": ["They nurse up to 14 times a day.", "They are hairless.", "They are blind."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A solar eclipse is when Earth casts a shadow on the Moon.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the tallest waterfall in eastern North America?", "correct_answer": "Pissing Mare Falls", "incorrect_answers": ["Pissing Horse Falls", "Pissing Elephant Falls", "Pissing Buffalo Falls"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the name of the high school in the movie Porkys which Pee Wee and the other boys attended?", "correct_answer": "Angel Beach", "incorrect_answers": ["Seward County", "Sandy Beach", "Palm County"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was the first Australian actress to win the Academy Award for Best Actress?", "correct_answer": "Nicole Kidman", "incorrect_answers": ["Cate Blanchett", "Naomi Watts", "Judy Davis"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the meaning of the prefix paleo (as in the Paleolithic Age)?", "correct_answer": "Old", "incorrect_answers": ["Meso", "New", "Modern"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What year was the musical romantic comedy Another Cinderella Story released?", "correct_answer": "2008", "incorrect_answers": ["2005", "2009", "2000"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "His brother was boxing heavyweight champ. He fought Tyson for the heavyweight title, but lost in an early round KO.  Who was he?", "correct_answer": "Michal Spinks", "incorrect_answers": ["Steve Norton", "Johnny Fullmer", "Danny Lewis"]}]